[{"answer": "Well, Piers, that's what everyone here really wants to know when it comes to that cease- fire that is meant to have been implemented immediately, the moment the U.N. resolution passed.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "When do you think we may see some military action?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "Yes, and that's pretty much the way people here feel, too.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "I mean, it would seem to most impartial observers here that he's calling everyone's bluff as usual, isn't it?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "In reading the president's statement, I think for sure a no-fly zone and perhaps strikes against some of the Libyan capabilities being used against the opposition -- yes, I think that's what you read into it for sure.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "Is that your reading of what's going on?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "Well, I think, specifically, what I -- what I've read in a statement, in the president's statement and in talking to others, that the U.S. will provide the enablers, the jamming aircraft, the tanker aircraft perhaps, the airborne radar control aircraft and perhaps some aircraft to map the ground, do the ground radar mapping so they know where the enemy forces are -- the enablers.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "Is that what you would expect?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "I think -- I think the time I've given him -- I mean, I think he's going to continue to attack.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "What do you give him, days, hours?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "Well, and that's where I see the contradiction in our plans at this point.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "So, presumably, we are looking at a fight to the end of his regime and him, aren't we?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "Well, we are talking about the Fukushima Daiichi power plant.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "Is that correct?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "Well, as far as we have monitored radiation levels in the vicinity, those figures indicate overall the radiation levels are not as serious as we had expected.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "Then, can we be confident that you know exactly what the situation is, or is it very difficult to properly assess given the dangerous level of radiation?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Well, you know, this is -- the tragic and gigantic disaster, you know, combined with quakes, tsunamis, and nuclear incidents.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Do you accept that criticism as valid?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Well, as a matter of our energy policy, nuclear power plants have been very important.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Can I ask what the situation is now in regard to the Japanese nuclear energy program in general?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "Well, we are making every effort to control the situation, and we are assisted by international experts, including the International Atomic Energy Agency and the U.S. experts.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "Do you have any idea when you may be able to bring these nuclear plants under some kind of proper control?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Well, I think most of the danger is confined to the area, obviously, in the plant and certainly of the surrounding areas, the 20-kilometer evacuation area.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "What is your assessment of the current danger of the radiation leaking?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "Well, I think all evidence points to no.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "Should we be concern about this?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "Well, I think that the nuclear industry has met its maker in the marketplace.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Surely, we shouldn't be considering the end of nuclear energy, should we?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "Well, I was able to pass legislation in 2002 requiring the distribution of potassium iodide, that is the protection against thyroid cancer out to a 20-mile radius.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "In the Soviet Union, the government was not transparent during the Chernobyl crisis.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "Should America now be getting more forcefully involved over there to try to get proper answers?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Well, definitely.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "How bad was it?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "Finally, have you been tested for radiation since you got back?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "I don't think there is truth to this allegation.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "Ambassador, how do you respond to Prime Minister Netanyahu's allegation that you're too timid to stand up to Hamas?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "Well, this is an Israeli viewpoint.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "And if you insist on putting any Hamas representatives into government, then there simply can't be any deal?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "Well, I think the international community is tired and running impatient with Israeli attempts to preserve the status quo.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "What would you say to that?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it might make our life easier.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "Would that have made life easier for everybody?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Well, firstly, that I have to go on a diet.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "What do you think when you see that picture?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "If it holds, yes.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "Do you think that pulling off a peace deal might be the greatest legacy you could give your brother?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "I thought it was a great interview.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "Alan, what did you make of that interview last night?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "Yes, I think he could, but he would have to know it didn't cost Israel its security.", "docId": "110318pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "Do you think he's the kind of man who can actually make a decision which brought a peace deal but cost him his job?", "qSentId": 490}]